Sajit Gurubacharya

Svdnev. Australia

 1. +61 0416 446 226
 | ■ sazit@live.com | in linkedin.com/in/sazit

About

An early career professional with 4 years of experience in data analytics, modelling and engineering across financial services, healthcare and government. Comfortable with both technical challenges and stakeholder management. Motivated problem solver and continuous learner who always welcomes feedback. Seeking roles in data and software engineering.

Education

Western Sydney University

Sydney, Australia

2017 - 2019

Bachelor of Computer Science

- GPA 6.75/7, High Distinction Average, Dean's Merit List 2017, 2018, 2019
- Founder and President of the Western Association of Computing and Mathematics
- Member of the Vice Chancellor's International Student Advisory Committee
- Awarded The Academy's "Above and Beyond Award" by the Chancellor
- Vacation Research Scholar at The Australian Mathematical Sciences Institute (AMSI)

Work Experience

KPMG Australia Sydney, Australia

Manager, Data Platforms

Jul 2023 - Present

• Azure Data Platform Implementation in Healthcare:

Lead development of configuration driven ETL pipeline using Azure Data Factory for batch loads on SQL and API sources. Developed cleansing and curation scripts using pyspark on Databricks to store data on the Delta Lake. Deployed Azure services using IaC (Terraform) and built CICD pipelines on Azure DevOps Managed the project budget and facilitated sprint planning and retro sessions on Azure Boards/Mural.

· Winner and Team Lead for the KPMG Futures Next Gen Al Hackathon 2023 on incorporating Al across migration services.

Senior Consultant Nov 2021 - Jul 2023

- Data Modelling for Pharmaceutical: Developed conceptual, logical and physical Kimball dimensional models for across patient, drug and finance domains mapping attributes along with outlining transformations required from source datasets.
- Data Modelling for Mining: Developed Kimball dimensional models across finance, worker safety and vehicle maintenance domains along with crafting the SQL queries used to build the data warehouse on Snowflake.
- Data Strategy for State Government: Assessed the client's digital landscape and delivered current state, target state, prioritisation roadmap and operating model elements to significantly uplift their data capability based on their expected funding.
- Data Strategy for State Government: Assessed the client's spending and utility of existing SaaS products and undertook market research and cost-benefit analysis to recommend ways to reduce cost and focus on best-of-breed solutions.
- Technical Domains: Python, SQL, CI/CD, Git, IaC, Azure (ADF, CosmosDb, ADLS Gen2, VNets, IAM), Databricks, Snowflake

PwC Australia Sydney, Australia

Graduate, Data Assurance

Jan 2020 - Nov 2021

· Data Analytics for Financial Services:

Developed a credit risk exposure model which captured material inaccuracies in regulatory reporting calculations. Performed data lineage across the bank's liquidity data stores for Economic and Financial Statistics reporting standards. Combined datasets and developed dashboards showcasing the bank's entire home and personal loan portfolio. Built an automated web crawler to retrieve loan rates from websites and assessed against rates charged to customers.

- Payroll Remediation: Analysed employee payslips spanning across decades of large listed corporations and assessed it against Enterprise Agreement Contracts to calculate required back payment amounts with interest and penalties.
- Technical Domains: Python, SQL, Alteryx, QlikSense, PowerBI
- Financial Domains: BCBS 239, APS 180, Basel Pillar III, PD, LGD, EAD

September 27, 2023